[Music] we have
[Música]
gossip eh today we have a lot to do today we have a lot to
tenemos salseos eh hoy tenemos tela hoy
cut here but oh well,
tenemos tela que cortar aquí pero bueno
for a while eh We still have to go because do
para rato eh Todavía noos queda porque
you remember this click that
es que os acordáis de este click que
we saw in the last live and alofoke very
vimos en el último directo y alofoke muy
upset with ibai for supposedly
molestos con ibai por supuestamente a
custar of using Bots, I mean, everything comes,
custar de usar Bots o sea todo viene
everything comes from weol who gets angry with
todo viene por weol que se enfada con
ibai and calls ibai a rat Eh Well when he
ibai y llama rata a ibai Eh Pues cuando
had the thing about if I
tuvo ahí La Movida de que si los
hire them, I don't hire them I charge more
contrato no los contrato Yo cobro más
than you you charge less, what's the deal, what a
que tú tú cobras menos de qué va vaya
movie you've made up okay and it
película que te has montado vale y
turns out that ibai let it fall
resulta que ya pues ibai dejó caer por
through a question to another, the
medio de una pregunta a otro no lo del
thing about the Bots, it's not that in ki they inflate
tema de los Bots no es que en ki inflan
the figure that as gref says, that's
la cifra que como bien dice gref eso es
very ibai I mean ibai had already seen
muy ibai O sea ibai ya había visto el
wol's tiktok where weol said that
tiktok de wol donde weol decía que
he probably had more numbers, I mean
seguramente tenía él más números o sea
more zeros in the contract than IB IB sees it,
más ceros en el contrato que IB IB lo ve
comments on the tiktok what is
comenta el tikt de queé está hablando
this guy talking about, I don't know, trust it because he gets angry
este no sé fíate tú por lo que se pica
eh, and then you also say  Damn, I
eh que también después dice tú [__] yo
've seen people on YouTube talking
he visto a gente en YouTube hablando
nonsense about how he earns more than me, that I
payasada de que cobra más que yo que yo
don't earn money because my audience is
no cobro dinero porque mi público soy
Zlatan, I don't know what, I don't know how much, and I say what
Zlatan no sé qué no sé cuánto y digo
for. I mean, it could come out, it could and
para qué O sea podría salir podría tal y
say whatever he wants to say, I know,
que diga lo que quiera decir yo sabes y
and trust you, because they get angry because
y fíate tú por lo que se pican porque
Uno comes out saying that G because he
sale Uno diciendo que le G porque que lo
says it, that's it, what can I tell you because he
diga ya está qué te digo porque que lo
says it, you're not going to show the
diga tú no vas a enseñar la cuenta del
bank account to see who has more or less, you
banco para ver quién tiene más ni menos
understand me, stupid, I didn't hit him that hard
me entiendes tontería no le di tan duro
because he was sucking me off so I could
porque él me lo estaba mamando para que
get him Bad Bunny for the
le consiguiera Bad Bunny para la velada
evening, damn, I regret having sucked his brains out.
[__] me arrepiento de haberle mamado
How is it that that son of a [ __ ] is
el [__] Cómo es que ese hijo de [__] te
going to tell you that you use Bots, the son of a [ __ ] didn't
va a decir usas Bots el hijo de [__] no
tell me to my
me lo dijo en la
face, it's as if he were the ace
cara
and right now I'm
de as que tiene que ser y ahorita
going to throw [ __ ] at him too,
también lo voy a tirar [__] hasta
even I threw [ __ ] at him so he learns
hasta I le tiré [__] para que aprenda
to respect, no
a respetar no
[Laughs] no,
[Risas]
I already knew it, it's that yes, bro, they
el no yo yo ya loé no es que sí bro no
can't go out and talk like that. How is it that
pueden salir a hablar así cómo es que
that son of a [ __ ] is going to say that you have a
ese hijo de [__] va a decir que tenés
Bot here, what  ha it's indirectly
Bot aquí lo que ha es indirectamente por
luckily
suerte
this said No well he's going to tell you bro
esto di No pues que te lo va a decir bro
obviously he's not going to
obviamente no te lo va a
tell you Well let's go mmo cona pu host
decir Bueno vamos lo mmo cona pu [__]
very savory clip no guys
clip muy salseante no chicos incluso
I'm even a little shocked yes yes well well well
estoy un poco impactado sí sí bien bien
that gref eh When Willy's podcast came out
bien que gref eh Cuando salió el podcast
he said that well he didn't know
de Willy él decía que bueno que no sabía
if he would watch it I don't know what
si lo vería no sé qué no sé cuánto Pero
I don't know how much But then you see all the gossip eh I mean and he puts it there and he's putting it here to give it diffusion and now is when ibai hits him Ah he's going to save it he's going to save it well ivai let's say that it has played
bueno ivai digamos que le ha jugado en
against him something that he always does it does
su contra una cosa que siempre hace a mí
n't surprise me I was watching the
no me sorprende yo estuve viendo el
live I saw the final 4 of the Americas a
directo yo vi la final 4 de Américas un
little bit in ibai's live spursito and
poquito en el directo de ibai spursito y
Mario and suddenly ibai goes and says hey
Mario y de repente ibai va y dice oye
spursito Do you think that alofoke uses
spursito Tú crees que alofoke utiliza
Bots and it's something that he does a lot he's
Bots y es algo que él hace mucho él se
very good at asking questions in which he
le da muy bien hacer preguntas en las
pretends not to say something and have
que pretende no no decir algo y que lo
someone else say it for him so of course
diga otra persona por él entonces claro
spursito told him well well  I
spursito le dijo bueno pues yo
honestly don't think so and you and gref and
sinceramente creo que no y tú y gref e
vain haven't fallen out in a while eh
vain ya hace tiempo que no se caen eh
But it's been a long time since you've fallen out I
Pero hace mucho tiempo que no se caen
want to give you an example of this fight in which you
quiero poneros como ejemplo la pelea
both hear luar we
esta de en la que ambos se oye luar
should record a video of this for
deberíamos grabar un vídeo de esto para
the main page Because we could we could
el principal Porque podríamos podríamos
even compile I don't know if we're in
incluso recopilar no sé si estamos a
time all the times that ibai has
tiempo todas las veces en las que ibai
done this type of movement which are
ha hecho este tipo de movimiento que son
many eh I many I want to remind you
muchos eh yo muchos Yo quiero recordaros
for example that it's that you can't see
por ejemplo que es que no se pueden ver
yes with grf you can't see almost
si es que con grf no se pueden ver casi
any of them gref is really green from
ninguno a gref lo ponen muy verde por
behind eh And then they put on a very good
detrás eh Y luego le ponen muy buena
face because it suits them which
cara por el hecho de que les conviene
is something that suits me You know I say
que es una cosa que a mí Sabes yo digo
Well let's see man I mean if you don't like
Bueno vamos a ver tío O sea si os cae
the guy okay he doesn't like him but don't
mal el tío vale cae mal pero no os
hang out with him then you're not
juntéis con él no estáis luego
messing with him you know and gref eh
comiéndole los huevos sabes y a gref eh
many have come to me many have
a mí muchos me han venido a mí muchos me
come to tell me about gref's gossip
han venido a contarme salseos de gref
for my videos and my news and then
para mis vídeos y mis noticias y luego
you find them
te los encuentras
Eh After a while playing with him that as they finish me off he just
Eh Al rato jugando con él que como me
came to you a while ago
caban de te acaba de venir hace un rato
to  me but well that the fight
a mí pero bueno que la pelea que
they had when the IB only had the
tuvieron cuando el IB le só lo de los
days tributed to gref Okay man Don't get
días tributados a gref Ya tío No te
into that stuff What do you think But
metas esas cosas Tú qué crees Pero eso
ibai does that a lot Sometimes with
ibai lo hace mucho Él a veces con la
people I saw this I'm giving context
gente Esto me lo vi estoy dando contexo
David And you ivai what do you think But ibai
David Y tú ivai qué crees Pero eso ibai
does that a lot Sometimes with people
lo hace mucho Él a veces con la gente de
around him he throws questions that he himself does
su alrededor tira preguntas que él mismo
n't want to say so that someone
no quiere decir para que lo responda
else can answer and he leaves like that so what happens
otro y él se vaya así entonces qué pasa
that this has sat very badly with alofoke
que esto le ha sentado muy mal a alofoke
and westcol and I was there at that moment being
y westcol e yo estuve en ese momento ser
the moment when they talk because they
el momento de que hablan porque lo
said it about alofoke and then alofo came
dijeron de alofoke y luego entró alofo
into the call and they were all like that so well
en la llamada y estaban todos así
Eh if it's that it's
entonces bueno Eh si es que es lo de
always the same guys we spend many hours
siempre chicos pasamos muchas horas en
live and here even the smartest the
directo y aquí hasta el más listo el más
dumbest and anyone well sometimes he lets his
tonto y cualquiera pues a veces se va de
tongue go and says things he shouldn't
la lengua y dice cosas que no tiene que
say it's not worth it And then Ah it turns out that
decir no vale Y entonces Ah resulta que
ivay has seen this clip okay we don't know
ivay ha visto este clip vale no sabemos
if he saw it on Twitter or if he saw it
si lo ha visto en Twitter o lo ha visto
here at the salsería which would be more logical
aquí en la salsería que sería más lógico
ibai give a signal if you're watching it
ibai da una señal si lo estás viendo
here leave a  comment or something ibai
aquí deja un comentario o algo ibai
bans gref from his channel makes him
banea a gref de su canal le hace le hace
look worse than me in the middle of the
quedar peor a él que a mí en pleno
live stream while gref was
directo mientras gref miraba
momentarily watching DJ Mario's live stream I
momentáneamente el directo de DJ Mario
read a comment in his chat
Leo un comentario en el chat de este
where it was said that ibai had 72,000
donde se decía que ibai estaba con 72000
viewers and gref is surprised because
espectadores y gref se sorprende porque
ibai's live stream was not showing up
a él no le salía el directo de ibai Al
When he tried to confirm that IB was
momento de corroborar que si IB estaba
live, he realized that
en directo se da cuenta que tiene
his content was banned apparently not
prohibido Su contenido por lo visto no
only has he banned him from his Twitch channel
Solo lo ha baneado de su canal de Twitch
but he also gave him a follow on
sino que también le dio un follow en
Twitter let's see what happened to everyone and it will
Twitter a ver pasado a todos y nos
happen to us this is what it is
pasará es lo que hay
Okay guys what the [ __ ]
Vale chavales qué
Chales
[__] Chales
balls Hey guys do you think
[__] Oye chicos vosotros creéis que a
IB got bitten that the other day I said that
IB le ha picado que el otro día dije que
sometimes he throws the stone and hides his hand
a veces tira la piedra y esconde la mano
no no
no
[ __ ] What theu I just freaked out of course he
[__] What theu acabo de flipar claro
posted one in D
es que ha puesto uno en el chat de D
Mario's chat and it's 72k and I said why don't you
Mario y va 72k y digo por qué no me
leave me and I follow him this is starting to
sales y yo lo sigo esto empieza a
get interesting
ponerse interesante
I'm going to this game happened Hey he
me voy a este partido pasó Oye me ha
banned me from his channel guys or what was that  like it
baneado de su canal chicos o eso qué ha
seems to me
sido en plan me lo está pareciendo a mí
Wait wait Wait wait I want to
Espera espera Espera espera que quiero
say something because I want to say
decir una cosita porque quiero decir una
something by has stung that the other
cosita a by le ha picado que el
Hey guys do you think that IB
otro Oye chicos vosotros creéis que a IB
has stung that the other day I said that
le ha picado que el otro día dije que a
sometimes he throws the stone and hides his hand Well the
veces tira la piedra y esconde la mano
same thing that stung you when I
Pues lo mismo que te picó a ti cuando
released a video because you went to
saqué un vídeo porque te fuiste a la
ibai's party precisely without a
velada de ibai precisamente sin
mask hugging the others and it
mascarilla abrazando a los demás y
turns out that later you tested positive for
resulta que luego diste positivo en
covid okay you sent your agency to
covid vale que mandaste a tu agencia a
take the video for me And I had to
que me tirara el vídeo Y me tuve que
eat a strike for 3 months no
comer un strike durante 3 meses no
noosa I just freaked out of course he
noosa acabo de flipar claro es que ha
posted one in D Mario's chat and you're
puesto uno en el chat de D Mario y vais
72k and I say because you don't come out and I follow him yeah I'm
72k y digo por no me sales y yo lo sigo
leaving this game happened Hey he
empe me voy este partido pasó Oye me ha
banned me from his channel guys or what
baneado de su canal chicos o eso qué ha
was it like it seems to me
sido en plan me lo está pareciendo a mí
for saying that when he doesn't want to say
por decir que que cuando no quiere decir
things he asks someone else the question that you
las cosas le hace a otro la pregunta que
can't stand each other that he can't stand him or rather am I
no se soportan que no lo soporta o sea
right and instead of talking to me
cierto y en vez de hablarlo conmigo por
privately  he banned me it's a joke don't talk
privado me ha baneado es coña no habl
to me privately don't
conmigo por privado que no
stand you we're
soportándoos
not 5 years old no
que no tenemos 5 años no
guys anyway he blocked me oh my god it makes
chicos sea me ha bloqueado madre mía
him look worse than me
hace quedar peor a él que a m
brutal eh brutal Saint
brutal eh brutal San
fight I'm going to see if there's something else I'm going to
pelea Voy a ver si hay algo más voy a
see if there's something else gref yb eh Ah yes there is
ver si hay algo más gref yb eh Ah sí hay
another click there's another cli It's true that there
otro click hay otro cli Es verdad que
is B with yb they say that I unfollowed you
hay B con yb dicen que te dejo de seguir
on Twitter XD Ah Well I don't know I don't know
en Twitter XD Ah Pues no lo sé No lo sé
guys I've been talking to him a little bit
chicos Yo he estado hablando un poquito
privately because he talks to me
con él por privado porque me habla por
privately when it suits him but I don't know let's
privado cuando le conviene pero no lo sé
see apparently he has unfollowed me
a ver al parecer sí me ha dejado de
on Twitter No because if not he
seguir en en Twitter No porque si no
would put here he follows you or something like that it could be let's
pondría aquí te sigue o algo así puede
see because when someone does
ser a ver porque cuando alguien sí Mira
follow you then officially ibanos does not
te sigue pues oficialmente ibanos no me
follow me on Twitter I don't know guys I
sigue en Twitter no sé chicos Yo es que
wrote to him recently to talk about the
le escribí hace poco para hablar de lo
narcis thing he didn't answer me and the other day he
de narcis no me contestó y el otro día
sent me this tiktok In which
me envió el el tiktok este En el que
well I say about alofoke and such that I
pues digo lo de lo de alofoke y tal que
comment on it like this because someone passed it to me
lo comento así porque alguien me lo pasó
in the chat as if asking me for explanations
en el chat como pidiéndome explicaciones
of  I heard about this and I said look and go ahead and
de heo de esto y le he dicho mira y vai
said what I had to say and that's it I don't
dije lo que tenía que decir y ya está no
know if something bothered you but Greetings
sé si algo te ha molestado pero Saludos
eh He didn't answer me yv is a person
eh No me contestado yv es una persona
that over time I've realized that he
que con el tiempo me he dado cuenta que
answers according to Well I don't know what it goes like during
contesta según Pues yo que sé le va en
the day So I don't know if there's a
el día Así que no sé si hay algún
problem the truth is if there is a problem he'll
problema la verdad si hay algún problema
tell me privately It's true that
ya me lo dirá por privado Es verdad que
there is and Ugh bad vibes bad vibes bad vibes well
hay y Uf mal rollete mal rollete mal
nothing family We stayed like this we
rollete pues nada familia Nos quedamos
stayed like this waiting for what he'll
así nos quedamos así esperando lo que
say and in the next hour surely I
dirá y en la próxima hora seguramente Yo
think they should have a debate at the salsería
opino que hagan un debate en la salsería
maybe the moment that ivai tells about
tal vez el momento que ivai cuente lo de
coku now that it's hot ivai tell it tell it you
coku ahora que está caliente ivai
looked terrible man
cuéntalo cuéntalo que quedaste fatal tío
you looked terrible with the cocu thing man
quedaste fatal con lo de cocu tío
you looked terrible and by don't get
quedaste fatal y by no te
burned Oh
ardas Oh
[Music]
[Música]